<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rejsedagbog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/dk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Rejsedagbog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>dk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/dk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Going Abroad / Some kind of introduction</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dk/posts/going-abroad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dk/posts/going-abroad/</guid>
      <description>All of a sudden I found myself without a plan, but with an agreement to stay at U.C. Berkeley for 5 months. Thanks to the help of Peter Sestoft, I found a plethora of other financial opportunities which would later turn out to make the stay possible.&#xA;This will be updated&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona, US</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dk/photos/arizona-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dk/photos/arizona-us/</guid>
      <description>The Grand Canyon is a steep-sided canyon carved by the Colorado River in Arizona, United States. The canyon is 277 miles (446 km) long, up to 18 miles (29 km) wide and attains a depth of over a mile (6,093 feet or 1,857 meters).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago, US</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dk/photos/chicago-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dk/photos/chicago-us/</guid>
      <description>Chicago, officially the City of Chicago, is the most populous city in the U.S. state of Illinois, and the third-most-populous city in the United States. With an estimated population of 2,705,994 (2018), it is also the most populous city in the Midwestern United States. Chicago is the county seat of Cook County, the second-most-populous county in the US, with a small portion of the northwest side of the city extending into DuPage County near O&amp;rsquo;Hare Airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About everything</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dk/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Sebastian, I&amp;rsquo;m currently studying a Ph.D. in Computer Science, more specifically on the topic of computing education. I made this small travel log to track my future endeavours abroad which starts August 2024. Hopefully I will find the time to combine my interests in photography with the many travels which lie ahead.&#xA;Specifically, I am embarking on an adventure to the U.S. where I&amp;rsquo;m going to be attending U.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
